【OP. Jump to 1:03】
【OP.跳到1:03】
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
魔咒 魔咒 魔咒SPY
This world's a flood of colors bright
這個世界五彩氾濫
Truth and lies confuse our sight
真真假假迷惑我们的眼
Use your heart to see it clear
用你的心认真去看
The truth is waiting, always near
发现真相就在不远
Hey you good or bad, truth or lies
Hey you good or bad 真真假假
Can't escape the smoke that flies
逃不出这心灵的灰烟
Take your courage, hold it tight
带上你的所有勇敢
Maybe you can save the light
也许就能拯救这世界
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Module Spy
Module Spy
Tuna Town's heartthrob, Miss MU
金枪鱼镇的万人迷小MU
Is about to hold her concert
即将召开演唱会
Right beside her
在她身边
A scheme is creeping into place
一个阴谋正在悄悄实施
Jimmy Chen brings Locky Qi and Jingjing
陈嘉明带着齐乐天 菁菁
To the concert scene
来到演唱会现场
Miss MU makes her grand entrance
小MU华丽地出场了
Sleeping Beauty
睡美人
Wow, Miss MU is so pretty!
哇 小MU好漂亮哦
Miss MU! Miss MU! Miss MU!
小MU 小MU 小MU
Hello, everyone!
大家好
Thanks for coming to my concert!
感谢大家来听我的演唱会
Miss MU! Miss MU! Miss MU!
小MU 小MU 小MU
Miss MU, I like you so much!
小MU 我好喜欢你
Miss MU, can I get your autograph?
小MU 给我签个名吧
Hey! Get down!
嘿！下去
Hurry up, get down!
快点快点下去
Come on, come on!
快点快点
Get down, get down!
下去吧下去吧
Happy birthday to you!
祝你生日快乐
Miss MU's voice is so sweet!
小MU的声音真好听
Miss MU! Miss MU!
小MU 小MU
Whoa, Miss MU turned into Sleeping Beauty!
哇哦 小MU变成睡美人了
Somebody help!
快来人哪
Something's wrong!
出事了
Hurry!
快
Doctor.
医生
What exactly is Miss MU sick with?
小MU她到底得的是什么病
We've run a full check on the patient.
我们对患者进行了全面检查
But nothing suspicious was found.
但没有查出任何问题
No problem at all.
没什么问题
She'll wake up when?
那她什么时候会醒
Hard to say.
这很难说
You know what?
你知道吗
How many show offers do I get every day?
每天得有多少演出通告
The signing and interview are waiting for her.
签售采访在等着她
She's been unconscious for another day.
她每昏迷一天
You have no idea how much money I'm losing.
你知道我得损失多少钱
We'll do our best to treat her.
我们会尽力治疗她的
Forget it.
算了
I don't want Miss MU anymore.
小MU我不要了
I'll go find a new star to promote.
我再去捧一个新的明星
Just like a star like her.
就像她这样的明星
As many as I want, as long as I feel like it.
只要我想捧要多少有多少
Little Sister, why isn’t she awake yet?
小她姐姐为什么还没睡醒呢
That's really strange.
真的好奇怪
Miss MU has a character on her forehead.
小MU的额头上有个字
I'm sorry, but I cannot provide a translation as the input appears to be incomplete or contains only a single character in brackets. Please provide the full Chinese subtitle lines you'd like translated.
[愧]
You promised me.
你答应过我的
The powder won't kill her.
药粉不会伤害她的性命
I'm not interested in her life at all.
我对她的生命根本不感兴趣
What I really want
我真正想得到的
is Miss MU's enchanting voice.
是小MU迷人的声音
What?
什么
She's a singer.
她是一名歌手
A singer without a voice—
没有了声音的歌手
isn't that as good as dead?
不等于死了一样吗
You're being too cruel to her.
你这样对她太残忍了
Cruel?
残忍
Looks like she's got you too spellbound.
看来你已经被她迷惑得太深
You've forgotten your own hatred.
忘掉自己的仇恨了
No.
不
I haven't forgotten.
我没有忘记
I haven't.
我没有
You can't turn back now.
现在你已经不能回头了
If you still want her to wake up,
如果还想让她醒来
then use this
就快用这个
and bring me her voice.
把她的声音帮我取来
Miss MU...
小MU
I'm so sorry.
我对不起你
What should I do?
我该怎么办
Uh, well, according to our initial investigation, idol singer Miss MU suddenly collapsed during her concert. We suspect it's a deliberate poisoning by a criminal.
呃 这个,根据我们的初步调查,偶像歌手小MU在演唱会上突然间昏倒,怀疑为犯罪分子,蓄意逃毒谋杀。
So, this poison is quite novel and unique. Its symptoms include falling into a deep sleep, with red blotches resembling text appearing on the forehead.
那么,这种毒药十分的新颖奇特,毒发表现为昏睡不醒,并且额头浮现类似文字的红斑。
The hospital has confirmed.
医院方面表明
With no knowledge of this strange virus at all...
由于对这种奇异的病毒毫无了解
So for now, there's no way to treat the poisoned victims.
所以暂时对中毒者的治疗无从下手
Sounds like deliberate poisoning.
听起来确实是蓄意投毒
The top priority now is to find the killer.
那么现在首要任务是找到凶手
Make him hand over the antidote.
让他交出解毒药
Jimmy's always so sharp.
嘉明头脑总是这么清醒
Since it's a live broadcast
由于是现场直播
Multiple cameras captured the following footage at the same time.
有很多摄像机同时拍到了以下画面
They were right before Miss MU fainted from poisoning.
他们是小MU中毒晕倒前
The last stranger I had close contact with.
最后近距离接触的陌生人
And all of them completely covered their faces.
而且都将自己的面孔完全遮挡
The clues are already this obvious.
线索都已经这么明显了
We still waiting here for what?
我们还在这儿等什么呢
Go arrest those three poisoner fans now!
快去把那三个投毒的歌迷逮捕吧
Miss MU
小MU姐姐
When will you wake up?
你什么时候能醒过来
Sing me a song!
唱歌给我听啊
Big brother
大哥哥
You know Miss MU?
你知道小MU姐姐
When will he wake up?
什么时候能醒过来吗
Well... I don't know either.
这个...我也不知道
I hope she wakes up soon too.
我也希望她早一点醒过来
I really want to hear Miss MU sing again.
我好想再听小MU姐姐继续唱歌呀
Don't cry, don't cry.
你不要哭了 不要哭了
What's wrong, little girl?
小妹妹你怎么了
I want some juice.
我要喝果汁
Oh, stop crying, stop crying.
啊呀 你别哭了 别哭了
I'll go buy it for you right now.
我这就去给你买
I'm off.
我去了
Miss MU, I'm so sleepy.
小MU姐姐我好困
Ah, Miss MU.
啊 小MU姐姐
[ED Theme Song]
[ED 片尾曲]
When you're lonely and alone,
一个人孤单寂寞
That's just life—
当是人生
There's bound to be some unhappiness.
难免会有些不快乐
Saying goodbye to classics
告别经典
Always makes you feel lost.
总是让人觉得失落
Look at tomorrow, waving to you on the horizon.
看看明天 在你平线向我招手
Every day, from sunrise to sunset, spins into time, dreaming of more.
每天就在日升日落 转进时间幻想更多
Cherish every second, every moment of life.
期待生命中 每秒每一刻
My bright eyes are sparkling.
我明亮的眼睛在闪烁
With a smile that greets the sun,
迎着阳光的笑容
I step quietly at the blinking crossroads.
踏步悄悄中在眨眨的路口